None of that is true of course. Some of you may have believed it. No proof is
more diverse than the average.
As you know, we have all the papers and not the papers.
Well, as a St. Edward alumnus, this is a great honor for me to find my glasses.
A great honor for me to introduce our most, our most revered alumnus, Jack Kahl,
whose fingerprints are on every success our school has achieved in its many
years of existence.
Thumbnail sketch, Jack is a self-made millionaire who is proud of his humble
beginnings in the projects on the west side.
After graduating from St. Ed's, Jack went on to be John Farrell, and upon
graduating, he ended the business world, selling duct tape.
He really believed in the product, and eventually he bought the company which
became Manko.
Subsequently, he and Sam Walton became acquainted.
They believed in each other, which led to Manko tape being the only duct tape
sold in every Walmart store in the country.
As Walmart became bigger, so did Manko. Although Jack became a multi-millionaire,
and he became a philanthropist of heroic proportions.
Pecano's name was on a building at John Carroll, and on a major addition at St.
Ed's.
Jack served on the St. Edward Board of Trustees for 25 years, and now his two
sons are on the board.
Whoever St. Ed's needs something, the Cale family is on their speed dialing.
Jack is now 75, and his five children and 14 grandchildren all live within five
minutes of it.
Now he's less than a minute away from us.
Probably let me say, here's Jack Cale.
[applause]
Jack, would you remind everybody that I have the books in the trunk of my car,
for only $15.
I think you just did.